Guide to the Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky and Lieberman Legal Files TAM.287
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Case Files, 1922-1988
  - Berman v. NMU: Plaintiffs - Roman, Miguel, 1958-1959 (Box 1d, Folder 29)
  - Berman v. NMU: Plaintiffs - Rydell, Roy, 1956-1960 (Box 1d, Folder 30)
  - Berman v. NMU: Plaintiffs - Southwick, John, 1957-1959 (Box 1d, Folder 31)
  - Berman v. NMU: Plaintiffs - Torres, Angel, 1957-1959 (Box 1d, Folder 32)
  - Berman v. NMU: Plaintiffs -Walker, Robert, 1958-1969 (Box 1d, Folder 33)
  - Biggin, William v. Immigration and Naturalization Service(I), 1970s (Box 1e, Folder 1)
  - Biggin, William v. INS(II), 1970s (Box 1e, Folder 2)
  - Biggin, William v. INS(III), 1970s (Box 1e, Folder 3)
  - Birnbaum, Norman, et al. v. USA, 1977 (Box 1e, Folder 4)
  - Birnbaum, Norman, et al. v. USA, 1978-1979 (Box 1e, Folder 5)
  - Blackstock, Nelson v. U.S. Steel Corporation, 1979 (Box 1e, Folder 6)
  - Boemer, Peter v. People of the State of California(I), 1970s (Box 1e, Folder 7)
  - Boemer v. California(II), 1970s (Box 1e, Folder 8)
  - Boemer v. California(III), 1970s (Box 1e, Folder 9)
  - Bond, Julian et al. v. James "Sloppy" Floyd, et al.(I), 1965-1966 (Box 1e, Folder 10)
  - Bond v. Floyd(II), 1965-1966 (Box 1e, Folder 11)
  - Bond v. Floyd: Research, 1966 (Box 1e, Folder 12)
  - Bond, Julian v. House of Representatives: Research, 1966-1967 (Box 1e, Folder 13)
  - Bond v. House of Representatives: Research, Undated, 1967 (Box 1e, Folder 14)
  - Braden, Carl v. Commonwealth of Kentucky: Clippings and Correspondence, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Braden v. Commonwealth of Kentucky: Formal File, 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Braden v. Porter B. Lady(Warden, Kentucky State Reformatory), 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Boudin, Leonard v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Passport), 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bundy, Sandra v. Delbert Jackson, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Camarata, Peter v. International Brotherhood of Teamsters(I), 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Camarata, Peter v. International Brotherhood of Teamsters(II), 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Camarata, Peter v. International Brotherhood of Teamsters(III), 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Camarata, Peter v. International Brotherhood of Teamsters(IV), 1978-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chagnon, Jacqueline, et al. v. Griffin Bell, et al., 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chaparro, Edilberto, et al. v. Stanley R. Reso, et al.r: Formal File (I) (Secretary of the Army), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chaparro v. Resor: Formal File (II), 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Chavis, Benjamin v. State of North Carolina, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Chinn, Ronald v. AT&T: AT&T Regulations and Research, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Chinn v. AT&T: Briefs, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Chinn v. AT&T: Briefs (Including Criminal Court of NYC v. Chinn: Chinn versus Mounted Policeman), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chinn v. AT&T: Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Chinn v. AT&T: Formal, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Chinn v. AT&T: Related Cases, 1977-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Chodorov, Edward v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Passport), 1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Council of Federated Organizations, Schwerner, Chaney, et al. v. L.C. Raine y, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Countryman, Edward v. Mayor Edward I. Koch: Briefs(I), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Briefs(II), 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Briefs(III), 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Depositions (National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Drafts of Complaint, Research, Town Hall Meetings, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Formal File, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Memos, Town Hall Meeting Flyers, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Notes, Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Press Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Retainers, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Settlement, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Countryman v. Koch: Statements and Affidavits of Parties Witnesses (2 Audio Tapes), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Crockett, George v. President Ronald Reagan, et al.(I), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Crockett v. Reagan, et al(II), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Davis, Horace v. University of Kansas, et al.(LB), 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Dellinger, David v. John N. Mitchell(I), 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Dellinger v. Mitchell(II), 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dennis, Eugene, et al. v. USA, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Deutsche Film-Aktiengesellschaft (DEFA-VEB) Aussenhandel (Film Organ of the German Democratic Republic) v. Kennedy, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Dolan, Dorothy and Marie Goggins v. Surrogate's Court of Bronx County, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Domingo, Silme, Estate of v. Ferdinand Marcos, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Douds, Charles T. (National Labor Relations Board) v. Wholesale and Warehouse Workers Union, Local 65, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 7a)
  - Dupree, Eugene v. USA (Coast Guard Screenings): Charles Colcord, 1952-1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Dupree v. USA: Ed Homer, 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Dupree v. USA: Kenneth McCrew (Pleadings), 1944, 1951-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Dupree v. USA: Correspondence, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Dupree v. USA: Correspondence, 1958-1967 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Dupree v. USA: Miscellaneous, 1957-1960 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Federal Campaign Funds Suit(ACLU) (I), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Federal Campaign Funds Suit(ACLU) (II), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Federal Election Committee v. Hall-Tyner Election Campaign Committee, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Ferguson, Herman v. Board of Education City of New York, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Fine, Daniel: Discharge Review Board(Navy), 1940s, 1979, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Fine: Discharge Review Board, 1957, 1960s, 1979-1980 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Fine: Discharge Review Board, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley, et al. v. Secretary of State, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Foreman, Clark Howell v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Passport), 1954 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Friedberg, Neal M. v. Stanley Resor(I), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Friedberg v. Resor(II), 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Gatti, John v. International Association of Machinists: Briefs, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Gatti, John v. International Association of Machinists: Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Gatti, John v. International Association of Machinists: Drafts and Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Gatti, John v. International Association of Machinists: Formal, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Gelfaud, Alan v. USA, Socialist Workers Party, et al.(I), 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Gelfaud v. USA(II), 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Gelfaud v. USA(III), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Gelfaud v. USA(IV), 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Gordon, Duncan et al. v. Winton M. Blount (Civil Service Commission): Briefs, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Gordon v. Blount: Correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Gordon v. Blount: Formal, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gordon v. Blount: Miscellaneous, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Grafton, Samuel et al. v. Brooklyn Law School: Briefs, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Grafton v. Brooklyn Law School: Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Grafton v. Brooklyn Law School: Notes and Research, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Graham, Edgar W. v. Commandant of the US Coast Guard Alfred C. Richmond: Briefs (I), 1951-1960 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Graham v. Richmond: Briefs (II), 1958-1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Graham v. Richmond: Correspondence (I), 1957-1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Graham v. Richmond: Correspondence (II), 1957-1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Graham v. Richmond: Miscellaneous, 1932-1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Graham v. Richmond: Miscellaneous, 1957-1964 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Graham v. Richmond: Court of Appeals, 1957-1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Green, Gilbert v. Board of Elections of the City of NY: Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Green v. Board of Elections of the City of NY: Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Green v. Board of Elections of the City of NY: Research, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Green v. Board of Elections of the City of NY: US Court of Appeals, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Green v. Board of Elections of the City of NY: Supreme Court, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Gwathmey, Robert v. Town of East Hampton: Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Gwathmey v. East Hampton: Formal, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Gwathmey v. East Hampton: General, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Gwathmey v. East Hampton: Research, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Gwathmey v. East Hampton: Research, Flag-Related Ephemera, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9a)
  - Halkin, Adele v. Richard Helms: Briefs (I), 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Halkin v. Helms: Briefs (II), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Halkin v. Helms: Memos, 1967-1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Halperin, Morton, et al. v. Henry Kissinger, et al., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Hampton, Iberia et al. v. City of Chicago, Edward V. Hanrahan, et al.(Black Panthers; Mark Clark; FBI; Emergency Civil Liberties Committee): Boudin Article, Drafts, Correspondence, and Research, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Hampton v. Chicago: Barnabas F. Sears, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Hampton v. Chicago: Press and Correspondence, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Hampton v. Chicago: Briefs (I), 1970s (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Hampton v. Chicago: Briefs (II), 1970s (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Harrington, Michael J. v. William E. Colby, et al.: CIA Activities (Director of the CIA George Bush; Committee on Foreign Relations; Iran; Chile), Undated, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Harrington v. Colby: CIA Activities (Admissions), 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Harrington v. Colby: CIA (General), 1970-1974 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Harrington v. Colby: Congressional Proposals, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Harrington v. Colby: Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Harrington v. Colby: Formal, 1973-1977 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Harrington v. Colby: Harrington Actions, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Harrington v. Colby: Legislative History, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Harrington v. Colby: Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Harrington v. Colby: Research, 1974-1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Harris, Oscar v. The State of Alabama: Alabama Statutes(Prison), Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Harris v. Alabama: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Harris v. Alabama: Formal, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Harris v. Alabama: Formal State Proceedings, 1976-1980 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Harris v. Alabama: M.C. and T.C.'s Notes; Research, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Harris v. Alabama: Briefs on State Appeal, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Hayden, Thomas and Jane Fonda v. National Security Agency (NSA), et al.(I), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Hayden v. NSA(II), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hayden v. NSA(III), 1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Hehir, Patrick v. NYC Transit Authority: Correspondence, 1954-1960, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Hehir v. NYC Transit Authority: Legal Research, 1953-1956 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hehir v. NYC Transit Authority: Miscellaneous, Undated-1958, 1955-1958 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Hehir v. NYC Transit Authority: Miscellaneous Exhibits, 1946, 1954-1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Hehir v. NYC Transit Authority: Appeal, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Hensley, Bige, et al. v. United States of America, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Hensley V. USA: Legal Research, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Hensley V. USA: Signed Statements, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hensley V. USA: Trial Exhibits and Miscellaneous, 1963-1964 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Hernandez, Nelson v. Mitchell Lattimore, et al., 1978-1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Hobson, Julius, et al. v. Jerry Wilson, et al., 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Court of Appeals - Briefs (I), May 1905 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Hoffa, James R. v. William B. Saxbe: Correspondence, 1972-May 1974 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Correspondence, Jun 1974-Oct 1974 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Correspondence, Nov 1974-May 1905 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Court of Appeals - Briefs (II), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Court of Appeals - Briefs, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Court of Appeals - Briefs, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Court of Appeals - Supplemental Brief, 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 1)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Defendant's Production of Documents, 1969-1974 (Box 10a, Folder 2)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Depositions - Carlson, Norman A., Apr 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Depositions - Exhibits, May 1967-1974 (Box 10a, Folder 4)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Depositions - Mitchell, John, Apr 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Depositions - Notes, May 1905 (Box 10a, Folder 6)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Depositions - Traylor, Lawrence and Dean, John, 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 7)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Detroit Actions, 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 8)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Evidence, 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 9)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Exhibits to Government Motion to Dismiss, 1967-1972 (Box 10a, Folder 10)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Government's Brief and Supporting Documents, 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 11)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Hoffa's Commutation Documents, 1967-1974 (Box 10a, Folder 12)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Hoffa's Convictions, 1973 (Box 10a, Folder 13)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Hoffa's Parole Documents, 1971-1975 (Box 10a, Folder 14)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Index, 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 15)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Documents (I), 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 16)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Documents (II), 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 17)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Documents (III), 1974 (Box 10a, Folder 18)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Memoranda, 1973-1974 (Box 10b, Folder 1)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Research - Pardons (I), Undated (Box 10b, Folder 2)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Research - Pardons (II), Undated (Box 10b, Folder 3)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Research - Pardons (III), Undated (Box 10b, Folder 4)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Legal Research - Pardons (IV), Undated (Box 10b, Folder 5)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: New Facts, 1974 (Box 10b, Folder 6)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Past Pardons and Commutations, 1960-1978 (Box 10b, Folder 7)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Plaintiffs' Brief and Motion for Summary Judgment, May 1974 (Box 10b, Folder 8)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Press Clippings, May 1905-1977 (Box 10b, Folder 9)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Prison Regulations, 1962-1974 (Box 10b, Folder 10)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Retainer and Fees, 1974 (Box 10b, Folder 11)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Sueability of President, 1974 (Box 10b, Folder 12)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Transcripts, 1974 (Box 10b, Folder 13)
  - Hoffa v. Saxbe: Various Notes, Articles and Research Materials, 1971-1974 (Box 10b, Folder 14)
  - Holtzman, Elizabeth v. Elliot Richardson, et al.(I), 1970-1973 (Box 10c, Folder 1)
  - Holtzman v. Richardson(II), 1972-1973 (Box 10c, Folder 2)
  - Holtzman v. Richardson(III), 1972-1973 (Box 10c, Folder 3)
  - Holtzman v. Richardson(IV), 1972-1973 (Box 10c, Folder 4)
  - Homer, Edward, et al. v. Commandant of the US Coast Guard Alfred C. Richmond, 1958-1959 (Box 10c, Folder 5)
  - Honiker, Jeannine v. Joseph Hendrie, et al., 1978-1979 (Box 10c, Folder 6)
  - Hunter, Eleanor v. Senator Joseph R. McCarthy, 1953-1954 (Box 10c, Folder 7)
  - Illinois, People of the State of v. Thomas Stewart, 1977-1978 (Box 10c, Folder 8)
  - Indiana, State of v. Ralph Levitt, et al.: Bloomington Defense Committee; Press, 1963-1964 (Box 10c, Folder 9)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Briefs, 1964 (Box 10c, Folder 10)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Correspondence, May 1963-Dec 1963 (Box 10c, Folder 11)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Correspondence, Jan 1964-Aug 1964 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Correspondence, Sep 1964-Aug 1965 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Exhibits, May 1905 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Formal, 1963-1967 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Miscellaneous, 1963-1967 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Levitt v. Attorney General Indiana John J. Dillon, et al. (Motion for Convening Three Judge Court), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Levitt v. Dillon (Summons, Verified Complaint and Exhibits)), 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Levitt v. Dillon (Correspondence), Aug 1965- Sep 1967 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Levitt v. Dillon (Exhibits), May 1905, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Levitt v. Dillon (Formal; Motion for Summary Judgement), 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Levitt v. Dillon (General), 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Indiana v. Levitt: Levitt v. Dillon (Raw Material; Drafts), Undated, 1963, 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Interchurch Center, et al. v. The National Black Economic Development Conference, et al., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, et al. v. John Mitchell, et al.: (I) (Second Amendment Complaint), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Institute for Policy Studies v. Mitchel l (II), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Institute for Policy Studies. v. Mitchell(III), 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Irons, Peter v. Griffin Bell, et al., 1976-1978 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Isserman, Abraham J. and William A. Reuben v Edward Levi, U.S. Attorney General and Clarence Kelly, Director of the F.B.I.: Administrative Index and Successor List Documents, Undated, 1973, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Isserman v. Levi: Briefs, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Isserman v. Levi: Correspondence, 1975-1976, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Isserman v. Levi: FBI Files, 1942-1947, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Isserman v. Levi: Miscellaneous, 1955-1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - It's about Time, et al. v. Seattle Police Department, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Jabara, Abeen v. USA, 1973-1983 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Jarrico, Israel Paul and Sylvia Gussin Jarrico v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Emergency Civil Liberties Committee; Frontenac Film Company), 1957-1960 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Jarrico v. Dulles: Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Jordan, Joseph, et al. v. J.C. Hutcheson, et al., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Kahan, Michael v. The Board of Higher Education of the City of New York: Briefs, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Briefs, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: By-Laws and Administrative Procedures, 1967-1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: College Review Committee (CRC) and Governance Plan Documents, 1973-1978 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: CRC Deposition Questions and Documents, 1973-1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Bargman, Abraham, Jul 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Creshevsky, Noah, Jul 11, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Fried, Vojtech, Jun 26, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Gittel, Marilyn, Jul 11, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Grass, Etta G., Oct 30, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Grass, Etta G., Nov 21, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Kahan, Michael, May 24, 1905-1978 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - King, Margaret, Nov 16, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Kneller, John W., Jun 15, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Kneller, John W., Jun 21, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Notes, May 31, 1905 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Park, Marguerite del Mastro, Jun 11, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Parkurst, Charles E., Jul 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Pollack, Bernard, Jul 10, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Reich, Donald R., Jun 23, 1978 (Box 12a, Folder 1)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Schmukler, Nathan, Jun 27, 1978 (Box 12a, Folder 2)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Stone, Solomon, Nov 21, 1978 (Box 12a, Folder 3)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Wedeen, Shirley, Jul 11, 1978 (Box 12a, Folder 4)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Depositions - Zagona, Helen, Mar 2, 1979 (Box 12a, Folder 5)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Exhibits - By-Laws of the Board (Exhibit 1), May 24, 1971-1977 (Box 12a, Folder 6)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Exhibits - Cases (I), 1975-1979 (Box 12a, Folder 7)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Exhibits - Cases (II), 1975-1979 (Box 12a, Folder 8)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Exhibits - Original, 1968-1978 (Box 12a, Folder 9)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Exhibits - Original, Copy, 1968-1978 (Box 12a, Folder 10)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Exhibits - Unmarked, 1977-1979 (Box 12a, Folder 11)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Formal, May 3, 1978-Jul 24, 1978 (Box 12a, Folder 12)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Formal, Jul 24, 1978-Dec 31, 1978 (Box 12a, Folder 13)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Formal, Jun 1, 1979 (Box 12a, Folder 14)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Kahan, Curriculum Vitae, 1975-1978 (Box 12a, Folder 15)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Kahan, Procedures Followed in Tenure Case, 1977-1978 (Box 12a, Folder 16)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Kahan, Recommendations and Evaluation, 1972-1977 (Box 12a, Folder 17)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Kahan, Tenure Correspondence and Materials, 1972-1978 (Box 12a, Folder 18)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Kahan, Works, 1973-1976, Undated (Box 12a, Folder 19)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Margulies, Sam, 1978 (Box 12a, Folder 20)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Minutes, Brooklyn College Department of Political Science, 1976-1977 (Box 12a, Folder 21)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Notes, Drafts and Memos, 1977-1980, Undated (Box 12a, Folder 22)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Proposed Trial Testimony, 1979 (Box 12a, Folder 23)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Research, 1975-1979, Undated (Box 12b, Folder 1)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Sezler Case - Correspondence, Undated (Box 12b, Folder 2)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Sezler Case - Exhibits, 1975-1979 (Box 12b, Folder 3)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Sezler Case - Kneller, John (Correspondence), 1977-1978 (Box 12b, Folder 4)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Sezler Case - Press, 1975-1978 (Box 12b, Folder 5)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Sezler Case - Reich, Donald Material, 1975-1977 (Box 12b, Folder 6)
  - Kahan v. Board of Higher Education: Subpoenas, 1976-1979 (Box 12b, Folder 7)
  - Kamen, Martin D. v. Secretary of State John Foster Dulles(Passport), 1955 (Box 12b, Folder 8)
  - Kasik, Arthur Frederick v. Alfred C. Richmond(See Graham v. Richmond), 1956-1960 (Box 12b, Folder 9)
  - Kaza, John Carl, et al. v. USA, 1978 (Box 12b, Folder 10)
  - Keen, Christian v. USA, 1978 (Box 12b, Folder 11)